Guide to the Office of Alumni Relations records, 1848-2005 RG0026
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Office of Alumni Relations records
1848-2010
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
RG0026
70.75 Linear Feet
Collection includes photographs and negatives, office files regarding Alumni Achievement Awards, and memorabilia.
Restrictions on Access
Series 5, 6, 15, and 17 are closed to research for 50 years from date of record creation.
Acquisition Information
Materials acquired through transfers from Office of Alumni Relations.
Historical Note
The George Washington Alumni Association (GWAA) was founded to strengthen the relationship between alumni and the University. There are alumni programs for each school at the university as well as associated alumni groups such as Columbian Women and the Society of the Emeriti. Alumni affairs reports to the Vice President for Academic Affairs.
This history note was written in 2005.
Collection Scope and Content
Materials in the collection includes photographs and negatives of President Trachtenberg, events, alumni reunion weekends, campus buildings, Distinguished Alumni Awards dinners, homecomings, alumni on the cover of Time, and Alumni Achievement Awards.
The collection also includes print materials regarding annual meetings, addresses, events calendars, publications, questionnaires, reunions, Honorary Degrees, special events, Alumni Directories, the General Alumni Association, meeting minutes, Cherry Tree and National University Law School yearbooks, and plaques. Materials in the collection range in date from 1848-2010. Note: Not all series are processed. Ask staff for assistance.
Collection Organization
Organized into 23 series: Photographs; Memorabilia; Alumni house files; Photographs of distinguished alumni; General alumni association files; Alumni association board of directors files; T-shirt; Binders; Contact sheets and negatives; Photos from old events; Historic materials; Images of distinguished alumni; Photos of President Trachtenberg; Alumni directories; General alumni association files; Yearbooks and memorabilia; Alumni association files; Alumni weekend; Notebook; Alumni files; Law alumni photographs; GW Impact, report on philanthropy; and a file on alumni killed in the September 11 attacks. There is no series 19.
Photographs; Publications; By-laws; Washington (D.C.); Directories; Awards; Events; Biography; Meetings; Reunions; Columbian Women, George Washington University, Washington (D.C.); George Washington University--Alumni and alumnae; George Washington University; George Washington University. Alumni Relations Office
- Photographs, 1975-1985; RG0026 Series 1; 2 Linear feet (Flat box 3, Box 2, Box 1)
  Scope and Contents note
  This series consists of photographs from alumni events, weekends, reunions, etc.. They range in date from 1975-1985, and were transferred to University Archives in 1987.
- Memorabilia, 1991-1993; RG0026 Series 2; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series consists of a GW smock, 3 Colonial kerchiefs, hat ("George's on my mind, GW alumni reunion '91"), and reunion coffee cup (1993). The material ranges in date from 1991-93, and was added to the University Archives collections from a backlog in 2001.
- Alumni house files, 1957-1985; RG0026 Series 3; 10.5 Linear feet
  This series consists of files and correspondence, and questionnaires relating to honorary degrees, reunion weekends, law alumni, library science alumni, Cloyd Heck Marvin, Martha's Marathon, awards receptions, Oswald Colclough, Colonials, Inc., regional alumni, tours, etc.. The materials range in date from 1957-85, and were transferred to University Archives in 1995.
  - SGBA Alumni Association, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - SGBA Alumni Association, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Presidents and officers of GAA Gov. Bd. and affiliated organizations, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Honorary degrees - memos, correspondence, etc., undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Hong Kong - Prominent alumni, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Rosters - GAA, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - George Washington Reunions, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Reunion-50 year, 05/11/1979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Reunion-50 year Correspondence, Memos, etc., 06/1967 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Student liason committee - booklet to recent alumni and students, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Reunion Weekend (info, packet), 1981 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Women Workers, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Insurance Program "Alumni Association Plan", undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Insurance and Bond premiums - correspondence, invoices, 1957-1966 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Insurance programs, Meyer & Asso., undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Insurance Programs, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Iran - correspondence, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Israel day, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Israel correspondence, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - International Business Alumni Association, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - King Tut Lecture, 02/12/1977 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Japan - correspondence file, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - King Tut Lecture - New York City, 03/13/1979 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Knox Lectures, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Robert Kramer, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Law Alumni Association, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Law Alumni Association - Membership procedures, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Law Association - 107th Founders day, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Lectures Program - Correspondence, reference materials, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Library Science Alumni Directory, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Marvin, Cloyd Heck, 1929-1959 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Liason Committee - University, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Lindner, Thaddeus - President of GAA - Correspondence, Memos, 1964-1966 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Life Membership - Copy of membership, Certificate, Historical Data, undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Life Membership - Certificates of, Prior to abandonment of dues, undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Mandate for the Committees, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Mandate for the Committees, extra copies, undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Martha's Marathon of Birthday Bargains, undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Awards reception, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Awards reception, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Awards reception, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Awards reception, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Awards reception, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Awards reception, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Auditorium, Lisner - Manager of lisner, correspondence, memos, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Condolences Letters, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Condolences letters, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Condolences letters, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Condolences letters, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Condolence letters, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Condolence letters, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Commencement - Spring, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Congress, members of who are alumni, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Colombian Women, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Congressional reception, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Chairs, alumni - correspondence, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Club, University - House Committee, undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Club, University - Nominating Committee, undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Colclough, Oswald Symister, 1959-1964 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Colclough Event, Committee for correspondence, memos, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Colonials Incorporated, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Course Audit Program Fall, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Student liason Committee - minutes, memos, reports, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Minutes - Faculty Senate, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Medalion - Correspondence, memos, etc., undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Members at large (gov. bd.) correspondence, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Minneapolis, undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Minneapolis/Chicago Alumni Lectures (Lilien Robinson), 03/27/1980 --03/29/1980 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Minneapolis, Past - Regional correspondence, etc., undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Nominating Committee - Gov. Bd., 1974-1976 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Nevada (Reno, Las Vegas), 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - New Orleans, undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Dallas Alumni, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Dinner Suggestions (Hotels)-Office, Minus, Diagrams, wine lists, etc. of B.C. and other hotels, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Detroit Regional Meeting, 1966-1970 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Detroit, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Denver: Sesquicentennial - Extra Copies, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Dallas, TX, 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Dallas, TX - Past Regional Meetings, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Dallas Alumni, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Dallas Alumni, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Chicago Alumni, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Chicago, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Chicago Alumni, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Chicago/Minneapolis Regional Meeting, 03/1979 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Commemcement (Spring), 05/04/1980 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Clock, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - China Day, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Cherry Tree, undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - CASE - Summer Institute, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Presidential Meeting - CASE, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Alumni Records Report, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - CHRONOLOGICAL FILE, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Alumni College, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Alumni Study, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Alumni College, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - DATA Processing - Addressograph and Records, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Alumni College, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Alumni College, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Alumni College, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - "American Society as a Technological Society", undated (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Jack Douglas -"Introduction", undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - MAILINGS - Printing, Postage, Handling, undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Originals and EAS Letter and Readings, undated (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - World Future Society Brochure, undated (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - London October 6-14 Dulles, undated (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - London September 8-16 New York, undated (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Orient September 8-23 San Francisco Cancelled- Moved to 9/1, undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Orient September 1-16 New York, undated (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Denver, COLORADO - Past Regional Meetings, undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Denver, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Condolence Letter, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Denver, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Denver Alumni, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Denver Alumni, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Denver, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Denver, Col. - Regional Meeting, 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Dallas, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Dallas, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Dallas, TX, 03/08/1976 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - North Texas Alumni, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Engineer Alumni Association (General Info), undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - First Wednesday - Spring, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Senate, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Regional Programs - GAA, Programs being conducted by other universities, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Regional APO File - GAA, Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Regional Alumni Programs Fall Semester and Spring Semester, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Regional Visits, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Regional - General, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Re-Evaluation Committee - Extra Copies of Report, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Re-Evaluation Committee, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Questionnaires - GAA, Analysis by Schools, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Questionnaire - 1965 GAA - Survey of Class of 1963, Instructions (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Questionnaires - GAA - Samples, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Questionnaires - 1965 GAA - Survey of Class of 1963, Metropolitan Washington (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Printing Costs, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Public and International Affairs Alumni Association, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Philadelphia - Regional and Telethon, 10/14/1971 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Philadelphia Alumni, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Philadelphia Alumni (New Regional Program), 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Philadelphia Alumni Meetings, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Pennsylvania University Alumni at GW, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Student Affairs, Office of, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Telethons, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Committees - Cov. Bd. (past) - GAA - Past Presidents Committee 1961 - Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Philadelphia - Regional and presidential, 1966-1970 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Presidents of the University - UNIV. - List of Past Presidents, since 1821, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Postal and Duplication Service Pennsylvania (Philadelphia) - Reg. - Permanent Correspondence file of 5 years ago and beyond, undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Phoenix, undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Portland, undated (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Plaques, Plates - GAA - Advertisements, etc., undated (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Plaques - UNIV. - GWU Correspondence, etc., undated (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Placement Office Notice - GAA - Reminder of Placement Office Facilities - Copies, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Regional - Pittsburgh - Past, undated (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Puerto Rico- GAA - Correspondence File, undated (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Publications Committee, undated (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Parents Day, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Photographs - GAA, undated (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Alumni Organizations, functions, etc., undated (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Office Presonnel - Memoranda, etc. re Past Employees, undated (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Oklahoma Alumni, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Opening Night Series, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - New York Regional with Dr. Kayser, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - New York Alumni, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Nominating Committee, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - New York City - REG. - Correspondence with Area Alumni, 1957-1959 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - New York City - Past Regional Meetings, undated (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - New York City - REG. - Correspondence with Area Alumni, 1960-1961 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - New York City - Basketball Game (Massachussetts University), 02/02/1971 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - New York City - REG. - Correspondence from 5 years and beyond, undated (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - New York State - REG (perm) - Correspondence with Area Alumni 5 years ago and beyond, undated (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - New York State - REG. - Correspondence with Area Alumni Past 5 years, undated (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - New York - Basketball Trip, 02/12/1969 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - New York - Basketball Double-Header, 02/27/1971 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - New York Meetings - Averall Harriman, 09/30/1971 --03/16/1972 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - St. Petersburg, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - St. Petersburg Alumni (Florida), 1978 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - St. Petersburg Alumni, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Florida Alumni - St. Petersburg, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - St. Petersburg, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - St. Petersburg, Florida - Regional Meetings, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - St. Louis, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Seattle Alumni - St Louis (Past) - Regional Mtgs., 1978 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Seattle Alumni, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Regional - Seattle, WA, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - "Speaking in Public", 03/19/1983 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Smith, Williwm P. - Tuesday Mtgs. with Jon Keates + Memos, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Student Survival Lecture and Reception, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Sponsor Evaluation Regional - Texas, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Tours, Caribbean GAA (cancelled) - Brochures, Memo, etc., 1964 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Tours, European GAA - Correspondence, Brochures, Memeos, Etc., 1966 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Tours, European - Charter Flight, Brochures, Information, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Tours, Epuropean GAA - Charter Flight Corespondence, Memos, etc., 1965 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Tours, European - GAA - (cancelled) Correspondence Notices, etc., 1964 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Tours, European GAA - (cancelled) Brochures Notices, etc., 1964 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Tours, European GAA - Charter Flight (Miss Brewer) Correspondence, Memos, Etc., 1963 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Tours, European GAA Brochures, Inf. from other tour taking groups, 1961-1963 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Treasurer GAA Report of the Treasurer, Statements, Memos, etc., 1944-1961 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Turkey GAA Correspondence File Tulane Alumni Travel Program, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Treasurer GAA Trust Fund of GAA (Riggs) State, 01/1969 --06/1970 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Twin Cities, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Utah - GAA Correspondence File, 1957-1960 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Virginia (Northern) Presidential Visits, 11/21/1967 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Virginia Suburbs - Reg. (perm.) Correspondence w/area alumni, Fairfax, Arlington, etc., undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Virginia Suburbs - Reg. Correspondence w/alumni in Alexandria and Fairfax counties, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Virginia Suburbs - Reg. Correspondence w/alumni in Arlington and Falls Church, undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - West Coast, undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Wilmington Delaware - Regional Meeting w/President Elliott, 05/18/1970 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Parent's weekend, undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Chronological file, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Chicago, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Chicago - Regional meetings (past), undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Chicago, telethon, 11/09/1971 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Cincinnati, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Cincinnati - regional meetings (past), undated (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Trust Fund "A" GAA - Correspondence, Annual Statement, Etc., 1956-1957 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Admissions, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Alumni Chapter, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Alumni Newsletters, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Advertising (misc.), undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Alumni Affairs Committee, Faculty Senate, 1982-1984 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Alumni Directory, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Alumni Questionnaire, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Alumni Survey, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - AMICI, 1882 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Art Alumni Exhibition, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Art Invitational Exhibition, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Authors, GW, undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Biennial Meeting - Governing Board, 06/30/1982 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Biennial Meeting - Governing Board, 06/30/1980 --1982 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Blood Drive, 08/13/1985 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Case Evaluations, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Christmas Card Samples, undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Colonials, Inc./Colonial Women, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Columbian College Alumni Association, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Columbian Women, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Columbian Women, 1980-1982 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Columbian, Inc., 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Continuing Education for Women, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Constituent Organizations (Governing Board), 1982-1984 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Creative Arts Weekend, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Development Office, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Diversions Brochure, undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Elliott, Lloyd H - President, undated (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Faculty Senate's Public Cermonies Committee, undated (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Faculty Organization Plan, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Faculty Senate, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Faculty Senate, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Faculty Interested in Alumni Programs (general correspondence), 1980 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Fun Day - Reunion Weekend, 04/13/1984 --04/14/1984 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - SGBA Alumni Association, 1983-1985 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Government and Business Administration Alumni, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Government and Business Admin. Alumni Asso. - Budget, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - GWU Club - House Committee, undated (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Hatchet, undated (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Health Care Administration, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Insurance, undated (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Ideas, undated (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Law Alumni Association, 1983-1986 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Leggette Room, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Library Science Alumni, undated (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Law Library Use, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Mail Service, undated (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Night Law School News and Public Affairs, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - New York Times - Selective Guide to Colleges, undated (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Nominating Committee and Awards Committee - Notices, undated (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Nursing Alumnae Association, undated (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - New Releases, undated (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Newsletters, 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Nominating Committee, 1976-1978 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Phipps, Sandra L. - Personal, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Pre-College Program, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Program Evaluation Form, undated (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Programs, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Postage Increase, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Public and International Affairs Alumni Association, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Recruiting Information, undated (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Reunion, 50 year, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Signatures (Alumni Relations and GAA), undated (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Smith, William P. - Memos, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Reunion - 50 year, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Annual Meeting - GAA; (Dinner), Correspondence, Notices, etc., 05/08/1963 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Annual meetings - GAA; Correspondence, Notices, etc., 05/09/1962 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Annual meetings - GAA; (Dinner), Correspondence, Notices, etc., 05/10/1961 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Annual Report - GAA, 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    General note
    Copy and Original
  - Art Lecture Series with Dr. Robinson, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Exec. Comm., undated (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Awards, Alumni Achievement - GAA; Biographical dates and names - No longer under consideration, undated (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Awards program and Dinner 1970; Sat. April 18th - GWU Club, 04/18/1970 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Awards Program and dinner Mayflower Hotel, 06/02/1967 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Awards, 25 & 40 year faculty, 1954-1969 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Awards, Ideas, other colleges, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Awards, Service Award - Biographical date of recipients, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Awards, 25 year faculty citations, memos, correspondence, name of printer, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Awards, 25 & 40 year faculty, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Awards reception, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Awards, 25 & 40 year faculty, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Awards reception - prospective places, undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - 1971 Awards program and reception Woodlawn Plantation, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Awards reception, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Awards 25 & 40 year faculty, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Awards reception, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Awards reception, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Engineering, School of - Univ. - Correspondence, Brochures, Notices, etc., undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Engineer Alumni Association Membership Procedures, undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Engineering Alumni Association, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Encore, undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Encore Lecture Series Fall, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Encore Series, undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Embry, L. Jackson - President of GAA - Correspondence, Memos, etc., 1966-1968 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Education Alumni Association, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - East Coast of Florida, undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Senate, University, 1962-1972 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Seattle, (Past) - Regional Correspondence, Etc., undated (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - SALT LAKE CITY - Regional Mtgs. Past, undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - San Diego Alumni, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 27)